Inventory of the Richard Wirthlin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Political Polling Books, 1968-1994 (Box 134-161)
  - 603-023-001. Friends for Dean Sellers Exploratory Committee: A Survey of Voters in the First Congressional District of Arizona, May 1, 1985 (Box 140)
  - 603-024-001. Realtors Political Action Committee: A Telephone Survey of Registered Republicans in the Arizona 4th Congressional District, July 1, 1986 (Box 140)
  - 603-024-001. Realtors Political Action Committee: Presentation Materials, August 4, 1986 (Box 140)
  - 603-025-001. AZ Citizens for Education: Transcribed Results of Arizona Focus Groups, June 1, 1989 (Box 140)
  - 603-025-001. AZ Citizens for Education: A Focus Group Survey of Voter Attitudes in Pheonix and Tuscon, Arizona, June 1, 1989 (Box 141)
  - 603-025-002. AZ Citizens for Education: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Arizona, June 1, 1988 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 3, 1982 - June 2, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 27, 1982 - May 29, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 27, 1982 - May 28, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 27, 1982 - June 5, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 28, 1982 - May 30, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 29, 1982 - June 1, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, May 29, 1982May 31, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, June 1, 1982 - June 3, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, June 2, 1982 - June 5, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-002-015. Goldwater Senate Committee: California Republican Primary Election Tracking, June 2, 1982 - June 4, 1982 (Box 141)
  - 605-003-016. Lt. Governor Campaign: California Followup Study, October 1, 1974 (Box 141)
  - 605-003-017. California Brushfire, October 1, 1974 (Box 141)
  - 605-027-001. Tom Reed: San Francisco Mayorality Race, April 1, 1971 (Box 141)
  - 605-027-002. Tom Reed: Conjoint Study Political Piggyback, June 1, 1971 (Box 141)
  - 605-027-002. Tom Reed: Conjoint Study Political Piggyback, June 1, 1971 (Box 141)
  - 605-027-003. Tom Reed: California Statewide Telephone Survey, June 1, 1969 (Box 141)
  - 605-027-007. Tom Reed: California 27th Senatorial District, July 1, 1971 (Box 141)
  - 605-027-007. Tom Reed: California 27th Senatorial District, July 1, 1971 (Box 142)
  - 605-027-008. Special Wallace Voters Study (Box 142)
  - 605-027-009. 11 Congressional District North - All Parties, February 1, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-027-010. 11 Congressional District - South Republicans Only, February 1, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-027-011. Tom Reed: 11 Congressional District (Box 142)
  - 605-032-002. Committee to Re-Elect Nixon: California AGG Run, June 29, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-032-002. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in California - Wave II, July 1, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-032-002. Committee to Re-Elect Nixon: California Statewide, July 1, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-032-003. CFRP Calif.: MOR Output, September 1, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-032-003. CALPAC/CMA: California Statewide, September 18, 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-032-004. Committee for the Re-election of the President: California Statewide - Wave IV, November or December 1972 (Box 142)
  - 605-064-001. Citizens for Flouroy: Republican Panel, March 1, 1974 (Box 142)
  - 605-064-002. Citizens for Flournoy: Republican Panel, May 1, 1974 (Box 143)
  - 605-064-003. Citizens for Flournoy: Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1974 (Box 143)
  - 605-064-003. Citizens for Flournoy: Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1974 (Box 143)
  - 605-064-003. Houston I. Flournoy: Voter Attitudes, August 1, 1974 (Box 143)
  - 605-064-003. Citizens for Flournoy: A Study of Voter Attitudes in California, August 1, 1974 (Box 143)
  - 605-067-002. RNC: A Study of Voter Attitudes in the 34th Congressional District of California, June 1, 1978 (Box 143)
  - 605-067-003. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the 11th District of California, March 1, 1979 (Box 143)
  - 605-074-001. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: A Telephone Survey of Likely Republican Voters in California - Analysis, May 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-002. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: Tracking/CFR, June 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-002. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: Tracking/CFR, June 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-002. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: California Tracking Republican Primary, June 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-002. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: A Telephone Survey of Likely Republican Voters in California - Analysis, June 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-003. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: A Study of Political Attitudes in the California Senate Race, August 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-003. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: A Study of Political Attitudes in the California Senate Race, August 1, 1976 (Box 144)
  - 605-074-003. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: A Study of Political Attitudes in the California Senate Race, August 1, 1976 (Box 145)
  - 605-074-005. Hayakawa Senatorial Campaign: Measuring the Impact of Political Media: The Shotgun Versus the Rifle, August 1, 1976 (Box 145)
  - 605-077-001. Market Optinion Research and The President Ford Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in California, September 1, 1976 (Box 145)
  - 605-077-001. Market Optinion Research and The President Ford Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in California, September 15, 1976 (Box 145)
  - 605-077-001. Market Optinion Research and The President Ford Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in California, September 15, 1976 (Box 145)
  - 605-077-002. Market Optinion Research and The President Ford Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in California, October 1, 1976 (Box 145)
  - 605-124-001. Seastrand for Senate: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in California 17th Senate District, June 26, 1980 (Box 146)
  - 605-124-002. Seastrand for Senate: A Telephone Survey of Registered Voter Attitudes in the California 17th Senate District, October 1, 1980 (Box 146)
  - 605-124-002. Seastrand for Senate: A Telephone Survey of Registered Voters in the California 17th Senate District, October 1, 1980 (Box 146)
  - 605-125-001. Friends of Paul Gann: Voter Attitudes in California, September 1, 1985 (Box 146)
  - 605-125-002. Friends of Paul Gann: Voter Attitudes in California, September 1, 1985 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-001. Colorado Republican Party: Special Cross-Tabulations, September 1, 1977 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-001. The Public Service Research Council: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Colorado, September 1, 1977 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-001. The Republican State Committee of CO: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Colorado, September 1, 1977 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-001. The Republican State Committee of CO: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Colorado, September 1, 1977 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-001. Jack Swigert for Senate: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Colorado, September 1, 1977 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-002. Colorado Republican Committee: A Panel Survey of Colorado Voters, March 1, 1978 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-002. Special Run for Richard B. Wirthlin: A Panel Survey of Colorado Voters, March 1, 1978 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-002. Swigert Senate Committee: A Panel Survey of Colorado Voters, March 1, 1978 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-002. CO Republican Committee: A Panel Survey of Colorado Voters, March 1, 1978 (Box 146)
  - 606-007-002. The RNC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Colorado First Congressional District, September 1, 1980 (Box 147)
  - 606-015-001. The RNC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Colorado First Congressional District, September 10, 1980 (Box 147)
  - 610-002-008. Market Opinion Research: A Study of National Attitudes, May 1, 1983 (Box 147)
  - 610-003-001. RNC: Miami Impact Study, February 1, 1975 (Box 147)
  - 610-003-002. RNC: Survey of Registered Voters in Florida 9th Congressional District, October 14, 1978 (Box 147)
  - 610-003-003. RNC: Survey of Registered Voters in Florida 11th Congressional District, September 18, 1980 - September 19, 1980 (Box 147)
  - 610-005-001. Florida Republican Party: Voter Attitudes in Florida, September 1, 1976 (Box 147)
  - 610-005-001. Florida Republican Party: Voter Attitudes in Florida, September 1, 1976 (Box 147)
  - 610-005-001. Florida Republican Party: Voter Attitudes in Florida, September 1, 1976 (Box 147)
  - 610-005-001. Florida Republican Party: Voter Attitudes in Florida, September 1, 1976 (Box 147)
  - 610-005-003. Florida Republican Party: Jacksonville Mayoral Brushfire, January 1, 1979 (Box 148)
  - 610-005-004. Republican State Central Committee of Florida: A Study of Candidate Images and Issue Perceptions in the State of Florida, January 1, 1980 (Box 148)
  - 610-005-005. Congressman Bill McCollum: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Florida, January 1, 1988 (Box 148)
  - 610-005-005. Congressman Bill McCollum: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Florida, January 1, 1988 (Box 148)
  - 610-011-003. Warren Briggs for Congress: Florida First Congressional District Brushfire, October 1, 1978 (Box 148)
  - 610-020-001. RNC: Media Pre and Post Tests Postman IV-A, April 1, 1983 (Box 148)
  - 613-006-001. NRSC: A Telephone Survey of Registered Voters in Idaho, January 1, 1986 (Box 148)
  - 615-002-001. South Bend Impact Study, March 1, 1975 (Box 148)
  - 615-002-001. South Bend Impact Study, March 1, 1975 (Box 149)
  - 616--010-003. Iowa Caucus Media: Commercial Evaluation for the Dole Campaign, January 1, 1988 (Box 149)
  - 617-006-004. Dole for Senate Committee: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Kansas, July 11, 1986 - July 12, 1986 (Box 149)
  - 618-006-001. RNCCC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Kentucky 6th Congressional District, July 1, 1978 (Box 149)
  - 618-006-001. Larry Hopkins for Congress: Extra Cross-Tabulations Kentucky 6th Congressional District, August 1, 1978 (Box 149)
  - 618-006-001. RNCCC: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Kentucky 6th Congressional District, July 1, 1978 (Box 149)
  - 618-012-001. Bush for President Campaign: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Kentucky, October 1, 1988 (Box 149)
  - 620-002-003. NRCC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the New Hampshire First Congressional District, September 1, 1984 (Box 149)
  - 620-003-002. Ted O'Meara For Congress: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the Maine First Congressional District, October 1, 1988 (Box 149)
  - 620-006-009. A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Maine, November 13, 1990 - November 14, 1990 (Box 149)
  - 621-002-001. Helen Delich Bentley: A Survey of Vote Preferences and Attitudes of Rand-and-File Republicans in Comparison with Activist Republicans in the Staty of Maryland, May 1, 1974 - June 1, 1974 (Box 149)
  - 621-002-002. Helen Delich Bentley: A Survey of Registered Voters in Maryland 2nd Congressional District, June 1, 1980 (Box 149)
  - 621-002-003. Helen Delich Bentley: A Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes in the Maryland 2nd Congressional District, October 1, 1980 (Box 150)
  - 621-003-001. John Burcham for Congress Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in the Maryland 5th Congressional District, October 1, 1976 (Box 150)
  - 621-007-001. Maryland Statewide Additional Cross Tabulations, March 1, 1981 (Box 150)
  - 623-006-001. Kellogg's: A Telephone Survey of Registered Voters in Battle Creek Township (Box 150)
  - 624-019-001. NRSC: A Statewidew Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the State of Minnesota, February 1, 1982 (Box 150)
  - 625-002-002. A Panel Survey of Political Attitudes in the 5th C.D. of MS: Trent Lott for Congress Committee, October 1, 1976 (Box 150)
  - 625-003-002. RNC: Mississippi Statewide, September 1, 1980 (Box 150)
  - 625-005-001. RNC: A Banner Report Based on Merged 1984 Data for Mississippi, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 150)
  - 626-003-003. RNC: Television Spot Study "Young's Record,", October 1, 1982 (Box 150)
  - 627-014-001. Cal Winslow for Governor Committee: A Telephone Survey of Republicans in Montana, November 1, 1987 (Box 150)
  - 628-014-001. Nebraska Statewide, June 1, 1986 (Box 150)
  - 630-002-001. Dan Hughes: A Study of Voter Opinion in New Hampshire 1st Congressional District, November 1, 1977 (Box 150)
  - 630-002-002. RNCC--Wilman Goldstein: A Surevey Of Voter in New Hampshire First Congressional District, September 1, 1978 (Box 150)
  - 630-003-001. Gatt Tables Thermometers: New Hampshire Republicans, April 1, 1979 (Box 150)
  - 630-003-001. Gate Tables Thermometers: New Hampshire Republicans, April 1, 1979 (Box 151)
  - 630-003-001. Gate Tables Thermometers: New Hampshire Republicans, April 1, 1979 (Box 151)
  - 630-008-003. Senator Bob Dole: A Telephone Survey of Republicans in New Hampshire, February 9, 1988 - February 15, 1988 (Box 151)
  - 630-008-005. Senator Bob Dole: A Post-Election Survey of Republican Voters in New Hampshire, February 1, 1988 (Box 151)
  - 631-001-001. RNC: Survey of New Jersey Voters, October 1, 1978 (Box 151)
  - 631-002-007. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the New Jersey 20th Assembly District, April 1, 1985 (Box 151)
  - 631-003-001. New Jersey Additional Computer Run, October 1, 1978 (Box 151)
  - 632-012-004. RNC: A Banner Report Based on Merged 1984 Data for New Mexico, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 151)
  - 632-012-005. NRSC: A Statewide Survey of Registered Voters in New Mexico, June 28, 1986 - June 30, 1986 (Box 151)
  - 633-001-002. Rockefeller for Gov: New York 34th Congressional District Overload, August 1, 1970 (Box 151)
  - 633-001-003. Rockefeller for Gov: New York 35th Congressional District Overload, August 1, 1970 (Box 151)
  - 633-001-004. Rockefeller for Gov: New York Albany County (Capitol District) Survey, September 1, 1970 (Box 151)
  - 633-001-005. Rockefeller for Gov: New York Statewide Survey: Special Area Cross-Tabulations, September 1, 1970 (Box 151)
  - 633-001-005. Rockefeller for Gov: New York Statewide Survey, September 1, 1970 (Box 152)
  - 633-001-006. Rockefeller for Gov: New York Statewide Panel Survey, October 1, 1970 (Box 152)
  - 633-012-001. NRSC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of New York, September 1, 1980 (Box 152)
  - 633-014-007. RNC: A Banner Report Based On Merged 1984 Data for New York, January 1, 1984 - December 1, 1984 (Box 152)
  - 635-002-005. NRSC: Survey of Adults in North Dakota, June 1, 1986 (Box 152)
  - 637-011-001. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes Toward Selected Republican National Committee Ads in the Tulsa, Tuscon and LA ADI's, July 1, 1984 (Box 152)
  - 638-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Oregon - Wave I, January 1, 1972 (Box 152)
  - 638-001-001. Nixon Re-Elect Committee: Oregon Statewide Wave I, February 1, 1972 (Box 152)
  - 638-001-002. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Oregon - Wave II, July 1, 1972 (Box 152)
  - 638-001-002. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Oregon - Wave II, July 1, 1972 (Box 152)
  - 639-012-006. Scranton for Governor Committee: A Panel Survey of Voter Attitudes in Pennsylvania, September 1, 1986 (Box 153)
  - 639-032-001. Republican Governor's Association: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in Pennsylvania, July 1, 1989 (Box 153)
  - 639-032-001. Republican Governor's Association & RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, July 14, 1989 (Box 153)
  - 639-032-001. Republican Governor's Association & RNC: Pennsylvania Republican Oversample, July 27, 1989 - July 30, 1989 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 1, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 27, 1980 - October 12, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 27, 1980 - October 24, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Governor William Janklow: A Survey of South Dakota Voter Attitudes, October 1, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 1, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 27, 1980 - October 4, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 27, 1980 - September 4, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 27, 1980 - September 18, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 642-008-001. Abdnor for Senate Committee: Tracking Report of South Dakota Attitudes and Vote Preferences, August 27, 1980 - September 24, 1980 (Box 153)
  - 643-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Tennessee, January 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 643-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Tennessee Voter Attitudes, February 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 643-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Tennessee Voter Attitudes, February 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 643-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Tennessee on State Issues and Ratings, February 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 643-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Tennessee - Wave I, January 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 643-001-001. Citizens Committee to Re-Elect the President: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Tennessee - Wave I, January 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 644-004-001. Nixon Re-Elect Committee: Voter Attitudes Texas - Wave 1, July 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 644-004-001. Nixon Re-Elect Committee: Texas Special Run (Box 154)
  - 644-004-002. Nixon Re-Elect Committee: Texas Statewide - Data, July 1, 1972 (Box 154)
  - 644-004-002. Nixon Re-Elect Committee: Analysis of Voter Attitudes in Texas - Wave II, July 1, 1972 (Box 155)
  - 644-004-003. Nixon Re-Elect Committee: Texas CFRP III, September 15, 1972 (Box 155)
  - 644-011-001. RNC: Houston Impact Study, February 1, 1975 (Box 155)
  - 644-011-001. Pre Houston-Topeka Study (Box 155)
  - 644-011-002. RNC: A Brushfire Survey of the 1st District in Texas, March 1, 1976 (Box 155)
  - 644-018-001. Market Opinion Research and The President Ford Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, September 15, 1976 (Box 155)
  - 644-018-001. Market Opinion Research and The President Ford Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, September 15, 1976 (Box 155)
  - 644-023-006. Texas Victory Committee: Texas Presidential Tracking, October 1, 1980 - November 1, 1980 (Box 156)
  - 644-024-003. Texas Victory Committee: A Post-Election Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, November 1, 1980 (Box 156)
  - 644-024-003. Texas Victory Committee: A Post-Election Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, November 1, 1980 (Box 156)
  - 644-024-003. Texas Victory Committee: A Post-Election Survey of Voter Attitudes in Texas, November 1, 1980 (Box 156)
  - 644-024-003. Texas Post-Election Analysis (Box 156)
  - 644-032-001. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in the Texas 26th Congressional District, August 1, 1984 (Box 156)
  - 647-009-001. Virginia Statewide Brushfire Study, October 1, 1977 (Box 156)
  - 647-009-001. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voters in Virginia 8th Congressional District, February 1, 1978 (Box 156)
  - 647-009-010. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in Virginia, August 1, 1985 (Box 157)
  - 647-009-010. RNC: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes and Perceptions in Virginia, August 1, 1985 (Box 157)
  - 647-014-001. Virginia Statewide, March 1, 1981 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-001. Bruce Chapman for Governor Committee: Verbatim Comments from Negative Screens Through the Name Identification Questions, November 1, 1979 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-001. Committee for a Positive Change: A Survey of Political Attitudes in WA, November 1, 1979 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-001. Slade Gorton for Senator Committee: A Survey of Political Attitudes in WA, November 1, 1979 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-001. Bruce Chapman for Governor Committee: A Survey of Political Attitudes in WA, November 1, 1979 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-001. John Spellman for Governor Committee: Tracking Report of WA Voter Attitudes and Vote Preferences, October 5, 1990 - November 1, 1980 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-002. Slade Gorton for Senator Committee: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in WA, September 1, 1980 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-003. Ken Eikenberry for Attorney General: A Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in WA, October 1, 1980 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-003. John Spellman for Governor Committee: A Survey of Voter Attitudes in WA, October 1, 1980 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-003. Ken Eikenberry for Attorney General: Tracking Report of WA Voter Attitudes and Vote Preferences, October 9, 1980 - October 15, 1980 (Box 157)
  - 648-018-003. John Spellman for Governor Committee: Tracking Report of WA Voter Attitudes and Vote Preferences, October 5, 1980 - November 1, 1980 (Box 158)
  - 648-018-003. Slade Gorton for Senator Committee: Tracking Report of WA Voter Attitudes and Vote Preferences, October 9, 1980 - November 1, 1980 (Box 158)
  - 648-023-002. NRSC: A Statewide Telephone Survey of Voter Attitudes in WA, February 1, 1982 (Box 158)
  - 650-007-002. Terry Kohler for Senate: Wisconsin Early Brushfire Republican Primary Voters, March 10, 1980 - March 12, 1980 (Box 158)
  - 650-010-001. NRSC: A Statewide Survey of Wisconsin Voters, April 1, 1981 (Box 158)
  - 698-011-001. Senator Robert Dole: A Survey of Republican Attitudes in the South, February 18, 1988 - February 20, 1988 (Box 158)
  - 699-002-003. Second Progress Report Computer Aided Restricting System, June 3, 1970 (Box 158)
  - 699-002-007. President Ford's Anti-Inflation Program: The Public Reaction, October 1, 1974 (Box 158)
  - 699-002-008. The RNC: Feasibility Report: Electoral Behavior Model, April 1, 1975 (Box 158)
  - 699-002-009. RNC: National Issues, March 1, 1975 (Box 158)
  - 699-002-176. Bush for President: Flash Results, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 158)
  - 699-002-176. Bush for President: National Survey, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 159)
  - 699-002-176. Bush for President: National Survey, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 159)
  - 699-002-176. Bush for President: National Survey, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 159)
  - 699-002-176. Bush for President: National Survey, October 7, 1988 - October 9, 1988 (Box 159)
  - 699-002-196. May National Merge, January 1, 1988 - May 1, 1988 (Box 159)
  - 699-002-196. May National Merge, January 1, 1988 - May 1, 1988 (Box 159)
  - 699-008-007. NRA: Analysis of Nationwide Surveys of Registered Voters, January 1, 1978 (Box 160)
  - 699-008-007. NRA: Attitudes Toward Gun Control: National Surveys of the American Electorate, January 1, 1978 (Box 160)
  - 699-008-007. NRA: Attitudes Toward Gun Control: National Surveys of the American Electorate, January 1, 1978 (Box 160)
  - 699-008-007. NRA: Attitudes Toward Gun Control: National Surveys of the American Electorate, January 1, 1978 (Box 160)